Guide to the Amil Gargano papers, 1960-2011 and undated RL.11364
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 7
  - Original Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 1
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Screening Reel, 1979 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-097)
      Pentax, Travelers, Harry and David, Barney's, IBM, Federal Express, Dunkin Donuts, Huffman Koos, Auto Train
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Reel, 1980 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-098)
      Federal Express, Pentax, Travelers, Barney's, Saab, MCI, Dunkin Donuts, Huffman Koos
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Reel, 1981 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-099)
      Travelers, Bay Banks, Federal Express, Karastan, Dunkin Donuts, Kayser Roth, MCI, Pentax, Saab, Time
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Reel, 1982 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-100)
    - Ally and Gargano--Untitles, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-101)
    - Ally and Gargano--Transportation Television, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-102)
      Fiat, Pan Am, Volvo, Hertz, Federal Express, Corning, IBM, Tonka, Pentax, Travelers, Barney's
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-103)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pfizer, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-104)
    - Ally and Gargano--Sanyo client reel, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-105)
    - Ally and Gargano--Timberland "Getting Soaked", Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-106)
    - Ally and Gargano--Union Carbide "Trying", Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-107)
    - Ally and Gargano--Untitled, Undated (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-108)
    - Ally and Gargano--WYNY Radio, 1983 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-109)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Amil Gargano reel 2, Undated (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-110)
    - Carl Ally--Agency reel, 1978 (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-111)
      Salada, CBS, Corning, Hertz, Fiat, Tonka, IBM, Pan Am, Federal Express
    - Carl Ally--Agency reel, Undated (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-112)
      Volvo, Centura, Hertz, Rise, Fiat, Country Club, Travelers, Pan Am, Tonka, Federal Express
    - Carl Ally--Australian interview, 1970 (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-113)
    - Carl Ally--Fiat European reel, Undated (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-114)
    - Carl Ally--Pan Am speech, 1972 (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-115)
    - Carl Ally--Pharmacraft Noxell spots, Undated (Box AV21, Film-reel RL11364-F16-116)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Editors, 1992 (Box AV22, Film-reel RL11364-F35-001)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" No leader information, 1992 (Box AV22, Film-reel RL11364-F35-002)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" No leader information, 1992 (Box AV22, Film-reel RL11364-F35-003)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Reel 1 of 2 rolls 1/2, 1992 (Box AV22, Film-reel RL11364-F35-004)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Reel 1 of 2 rolls 3/7/8, 1992 (Box AV23, Film-reel RL11364-F35-005)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Reel 1 of 2 rolls 12/13, 1992 (Box AV23, Film-reel RL11364-F35-006)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Reel 2 of 2 rolls 4/5/6, 1992 (Box AV23, Film-reel RL11364-F35-007)
    - General and Personal--LCI "They Shoot Films" Reel 2 of 2 rolls 9/10/11, 1992 (Box AV23, Film-reel RL11364-F35-008)
    - General and Personal--The Last Dark Days 27:35, 2010 (Box AV24, Video-disc RL-11364-OP-001)
    - General and Personal--Soldiers of Stone: The Painful Battlegrounds of America's War Dead, edited by Amil Gargano, unpublished, 2010 (Box AV24, Video-disc RL-11364-OP-002)
    - General and Personal--The Real French Connection--And Final Answer to the Biggest Thefts in New York History, unpublished, 2011 (Box AV24, Video-disc RL-11364-OP-003)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, 1984 (Reel 117, Film-reel RL11364-F16-117)
    - Ally and Gargano--A&W Beverages Presentation, Undated (Reel 118, Film-reel RL11364-F16-118)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency special historical reel, 1979 (Reel 119, Film-reel RL11364-F16-119)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency history reel 1, 1989 (Reel 120, Film-reel RL11364-F16-120)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel "good one" for Ciba Film presentation, Undated (Reel 121, Film-reel RL11364-F16-121)
    - Ally and Gargano--Amil's Arsenal A, Undated (Reel 122, Film-reel RL11364-F16-122)
    - Ally and Gargano--Hertz History reel A, Undated (Reel 123, Film-reel RL11364-F16-123)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business Presentation Reel 29 spots, Undated (Reel 124, Film-reel RL11364-F16-124)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers client reel 1 45 spots, Undated (Reel 125, Film-reel RL11364-F16-125)
    - General and Personal--Untitled, Undated (Reel 126, Film-reel RL11364-F16-126)
    - General and Personal--Untitled, Undated (Reel 127, Film-reel RL11364-F16-127)
    - General and Personal--Untitled, Undated (Reel 128, Film-reel RL11364-F16-128)